You're now a part of the Union,
so do as I fucking tell you, okay?
Fucking answer me, okay?
- Yes.
- Yes, sir.
Hello, brother!
Hello, sir!
What the fuck is this? The mafia?
Don't talk to me, or I'll kill you.
People will report the noise,
you dumb fucks.
We're sorry, sir.
Lower your fucking head.
Stand up straight!
Hello.
- Hello.
- You're here.
What the hell are you staring at?
Go inside.
Just a sec.
I'll only say this once.
Listen carefully.
I don't care what Park Hu-min
and all of you are up to.
And I didn't need to come here.
But I came… just to make this clear.
If I see you
around Su-ho's hospital again…
I'll kill you all.
I will kill all of you.
You need to separate
the variables to solve it quickly.
A fixed range variable
is no different from a constant.
MATHEMATICS
Keep your word…
and no one will get hurt.
Stop hanging around Hu-min.
Fine.
I understand.
So keep your word too.
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 2
Hey.
Don't look at me like that,
or I'll gouge your eyes out.
Is that fun to read?
You just let him go?
Then why did you tell me to bring him?
Do I have to explain it?
I mean, fuck,
why are you obsessed with Eunjang?
It's not like they bring in much money.
You know you can't outmuscle Baku.
Right?
So I need to make him come to me.
Did our boys go to his dad's restaurant?
44, 45, 46,
LIFE'S TOUGH
BUT IT'S OKAY. I'M TOUGH TOO
…47, 48, 49,
50, 51, 52, 53, 54.
DAD
Five more!
50, 60, 70,
80, 90, 100!
Yeah, Dad?
Hey, Hu-min. It's Officer Han.
Your dad got into trouble again.
- Can you come talk to him?
- Get back here.
How the fuck should I know
if it was real or fake?
- Tell the truth!
- Hey, Mr. Park!
- Come with me, and we'll talk.
- Hey, assholes!
Come here and tell them!
- I'll kill you!
- Park!
- Keep those kids quiet.
- Go inside.
- Why?
- Dad, stop.
Come on. Please stop!
You punk.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Why did you apologize, punk?
I did nothing wrong! Why say sorry?
Damn, please!
Park. I understand.
So let's go and fill out a report first.
We have rules to follow.
He wasn't a minor! I even checked his ID!
His photo too! Damn it!
Yes, so let's talk at the station.
You sold alcohol to minors, didn't you?
Fuck this, seriously.
Fine, let's go.
Let's go.
Officer Kim, get the kids in the car too.
Hey! Get in the car!
Hey, get in. Quickly.
Hey, I'm going already. Damn.
Hey, Baek-jin asked me to tell you
that he misses you.
NA BAEK-JIN
Where are you?
Let's meet tomorrow.
I'll send the address.
Keep your word…
and no one will get hurt.
Yeah, lower your stance a bit.
Keep looking straight ahead. That's it.
That's right. It'll become muscle memory
if you do it about a hundred times.
Good!
That's it.
- Yeon Si-eun.
- Si-eun.
What brings you here?
Are you joining our team?
If you want to join,
you'll have to pass our rigorous tryouts.
I met Na Baek-jin.
The guy in the Union.
What?
Baek-jin, that fucking lunatic.
Hey, well,
did anything happen?
Nothing happened.
I don't care what you guys are doing
but leave me out of it.
Si-eun.
What's going on?
I don't have as much free time as you.
I have a lot to do.
You guys have fun.
What the hell is your problem?
We didn't ask you to join us.
That's right.
So let's go our separate ways.
Okay.
I get what you're saying.
Fine.
Let's ignore each other.
Good.
Si-eun!
Baku seemed like
he was doing that on purpose.
And you too.
I don't know what happened to you,
but I bet Baku didn't mean what he said.
Don't let it bother you.
Jun-tae.
Yes?
It's just…
I'm more comfortable alone.
Now, that's it for transformers,
which are a typical example
of mutual induction.
Let's take a look at another example.
Hang on.
Hey, Eunjang.
Where are your friends?
Hey, didn't Baek-jin tell us
to leave this punk alone?
He did?
Let's just go.
Hey, where's Seong-je?
No idea. He'll be back soon.
Jun-tae, where's Si-eun?
He left right after class.
He left?
Man, what the heck is wrong with him?
Did you talk to him?
No.
Well,
I'm not sure, but I kind of have an idea.
I mean, I don't think Si-eun meant
what he said either.
I'll go ahead. See you tomorrow.
Damn, man.
Tell me you aren't meeting Baek-jin.
Nothing like that, man.
Take care. See you later.
Then where are you going?
On a date. Someone from Buil Girls' High.
Let's go.
Call Seong-je.
Where could it be?
I dropped my toy around here somewhere.
It's been a while.
How's your knee?
Why did you come here?
Hey, I don't see the newbie.
Si-eun or whatever.
Playing with him would be more fun.
Is it fun
to be Na Baek-jin's minion?
It is fun.
I get to kill punks like you.
Are you fucking counting?
There are four of them.
You're my playmate.
What? Are you scared?
Go, Jun-tae.
What?
I said go, idiot!
You're so fucking cool.
- You son of a bitch.
- Hey!
- Hey, fuck you.
- Get back here, asshole!
You guys are fucking ridiculous.
This place is no good.
Let's go somewhere quiet.
Don't glare at me like that.
You fucking wimp.
You son of a bitch!
Hey!
Where are you going, asshole?
You fucker! Get back here!
Hey, you bastard!
Man, that fucking asshole.
Hey!
- Go that way.
- Okay.
Fuck.
Hey, Seong-je.
You need me to find one more?
Yeon Si-eun?
Man, I just let him go earlier.
Yeah, got it.
PARK HU-MIN
This device is switched off. Please leave…
SEO JUN-TAE
MISSED CALL
SEO JUN-TAE:
ARE YOU ON YOUR WAY TO CRAM SCHOOL?
Hello?
Si-eun.
What's that message about?
I was just wondering
if you made it to cram school.
Why are you asking?
I just wanted to see if
you made it there safely.
That's why I called.
Yeah.
- Hey!
- Si-eun, don't worry about me. I'm fine.
- Go home after cram school.
- Hello?
Seo Jun-tae?
This asshole!
- You son of a bitch!
- Man, fuck you.
- Lift your head.
- Fucking bitch.
You wear this all the time.
It's my best outfit.
Now go get me some cigarettes.
Hey, let's split it.
Quit smoking.
Hey, give me a smoke.
I just quit.
We're not open yet.
Where's Baek-jin?
Baek-jin?
They're on first-name terms?
You must be fucking crazy.
- Seriously.
- Whatever.
Hey, isn't that guy Park Hu-min?
- Park Hu-min?
- Who?
- I've heard that name.
- Eunjang's top dog. Don't you know him?
- That's him?
- Keep playing cards.
He's acting so fucking tough.
Fuck!
Na Baek-jin.
Where is he?
It's been a while.
Park Hu-min.
I still think of you as a friend.
Joining the Union
is a good deal for you too.
After graduation,
it'll become a regular business.
It's all planned out.
You're actually a fucking dumbass.
Hey.
Fucking moron.
Do you still not know
why I don't do your thug stuff?
Or do you pretend not to know?
I just…
really fucking hate you.
I think you're the dumbass, not me.
What the fuck did you do?
How's Go Hyun-tak doing?
Hey.
Did Baek-jin say you can leave?
I doubt that.
I don't have time for this.
Let's make it short.
Son of a bitch!
Your punches are still as weak as ever.
You fucking…
Hey, we're not done yet.
Get up, you fucking idiot.
Fucking shit.
Fuck you.
Come on.
Fuck you!
Want some more?
Fuck! Kill him!
Shit!
Hey! Fuck you!
Fuck!
Hey, you son of a bitch!
Fuck you!
Fucking son of a bitch.
Can I leave now?
That's enough.
That's enough. He can leave.
Go see for yourself
to understand the situation.
How long can you hold out like this?
Hey.
You're not letting me go.
I'm leaving for your sake.
Everyone here almost died.
Fuck!
Hey, I heard Hyun-tak went
to fight Seong-je.
Fuck. Hyun-tak is dead.
Seong-je is a fucking psycho.
- Want to go watch? I got the address.
- Are you crazy?
Hey.
Stop it!
What the fuck are you doing?
Hey, isn't this guy fucking cute?
- Look at this guy.
- Don't do it!
- Fucking asshole.
- Stop it!
Stop it!
Man, fuck this.
Hey, you fucker!
Glasses.
Are you okay, Hyun-tak?
Now, time for a photo. Look over here.
One, two, three. For fuck's sake. Hey.
I said look here.
What's this? You sad?
Should I beat him some more?
Let's get this over with.
Now, smile big.
One, two, three. Say cheese!
Newbie!
I've missed you.
Today's been fun!
Is it my birthday or what?
Should I buy a lottery ticket too?
Whoa. You were going to stab me with this?
You're a fucking wimp.
This is no damn fun.
Fuck you.
Fuck you!
Let go!
That's it!
Fuck you!
Let me go, you fucker!
Fuck you, asshole!
You fucking moron. Fuck you.
Get up, you fucking bastard.
Fuck you.
So I have to
kill you to end this, don't I?
Hey, Si-eun! Are you okay?
Hey, Si-eun!
Su-ho.
I got into another fight.
I'm sorry.
Subtitle translation by: James Webb